

SAGAR KHADGI

Technology and Business Enthusiast

OBJECTIVE

A Skilled IT and Business personnel, graduated from Herald College Kathmandu in affiliation with University of Wolverhampton, with more than 3 years of work experience, aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of accelerated growth, business development, problem-solving and technical skills.

INTRODUCTION

NAME:

Sagar Khadgi

DATE OF BIRTH-PLACE:

01/06/1998 - Kathmandu, Nepal

MARITAL STATUS:

Single:

NATIONALITY:

Nepali

CONTACT

PHONE:

+977-9841179619

ADDRESS:

Baneshwor, Kathmandu, Nepal

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sagar-khadgi-49b295131/

TUTORIALS:

https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC2aOPzA09dGVDFo5B81GK6w

EMAIL:

sagarkhadai25@amail.com

EDUCATION

Herald College Kathmandu in Affiliation with University of Wolverhampton (UK) [2016-2019]

- Bachelor of Science (Honours) in Computer Science
- Qualification Awarded: First Class Honours [21/06/2019]
- Delegate to Thailand UTCC for "International Business Exposure Trip-Design Thinking Workshop (2018)"
- Third Position on Fortnight Scholarship United Kingdom (2017).
- Awarded as "Student Academic Representative (StAR)" for the year 2016-2017.

V.S Niketan Higher Secondary School, Minbhawan Kathmandu [2014-2016]

- 10+2 Higher Secondary Education Board
- Faculty: Management, Grade: First Division [19/10/2016]

V.S Niketan Secondary School, Minbhawan Kathmandu [2014]

- Secondary School, School Leaving Certificate
- Grade: First Division [13/06/2014]

WORK EXPERIENCE

ING Skill Academy - B2B Specialist and Project Management [Nov 2019 – Feb 2021]

- Daily Standups and Change Management with Priority.
- **Design New Campaigns** for Target Audiences.
- Supervise the Projects Undertaken.
- Analyze and Review the Campaign's Risk, Budget, Schedule and effort using Asana.
- Manage the Workflow and Operation using Agile Methodologies.
- Resource Management. (Branding, Merchandise)
- Strategizing the Plans and Formulation.
- Extensive Research on Course Development of Al and IoT.
- Conduct Cyber Security and IoT Bootcamps all over the Nepal.
- Curate (Technical) Live Sessions.
- Data Management and System Development (Google Sheets).
- Maintaining the Good Relation with POC all over the Nepal.
- Document the Future Escalation.
- Development of High-Level Dashboards and Daily Reports for upper management.

Herald College Kathmandu - Final Year Project Supervisor, Parttime

[Sept 2020 - Sept 2021]

- Supervising and Mentoring the Final Year Project (Dissertation) for IT Undergraduate students.
- Responsible as a Scrum Master.
- Track and guide students to meet the Milestones, Schedules and Timeline.
- Discuss the Project Progress and Continuous review of developed artefacts.
- Evaluate the Assessment.
- Motivate Students to complete the Project Artefacts and its Iterations.

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication and Presentation Skills
- Multitasking
- Work on Extreme Deadlines
- Problem Solving
- Leadership Skills (Worked as a Deputy Lead)
- Task Delegation and Prioritization

TRAINING

- Basic Android Development and Its Lifecycle
- Java Programming
- Start-up Weekend
- Foundation to Data Analysis by Google.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- Fluent English
- Fluent Nepali
- German A1
- Newari
- Hindi

HOBBIES

- Reading
- Photography and Videography
- YouTube
- Podcasts
- Football
- Guitar
- Travelling

EKbana Solutions, Software Quality Analyst May 2019 – Oct 2019

- Designing, writing and executing test cases and test plans.
- Troubleshooting, isolating and writing problem reports.
- Communicating with the project manager, developers, and fellow QA engineers to ensure project's quality and schedule.
- Assisting Senior QA/Project Manager to design the system.
- Raise Bugs and Assign to Developer team using Gitlab and JIRA.
- Ensure the Project Quality with constant standups and Project monitoring.
- Automation Testing using Selenium.
- API Testing using Postman.

Herald College Kathmandu - Business Development Intern Jul 2017 – Oct 2017

- Strategizing business plans and implementation
- Cold calling to high school graduates to create footsteps.
- Career and Education Counselling.
- Handling Leads Management Software.
- Conducting education fairs.

SKILL EXPERIENCE

- Curated CyberSecurity and Information Technology Bootcamp for more than 5000+ High school students in Bharatpur, Pokhara, Beni, Dulegauda, Nepalgunj, Dang, Surkhet, Butwal, Jhapa, Itahari, Biratnagar and Kathmandu.
- Live Information Technology Tutorials, Webinars and Podcasts.
- Leading the Herald College team in 'Design Thinking Workshop' held at 'University of Thai Chamber of Commerce' in Thailand.
- Associated with Top elearning Technology Company in APAC 2020. https://www.mysecondteacher.com/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Experience on Agile Development Methodologies.
- Project Management Tools like JIRA, Trello and Asana.
- Technical Content Writing (Business Case, Memorandum and Software Requirement Specification).
- Knowledge on Github and Gitlab.
- Experience on SQL and Data Analysis.
- Knowledge on OOP Language.
- Data Visualisation using Tableau.
- MS Office (Word, Google Sheets, Excel, PowerPoint, Visio).
- Experience on drawing **UML Diagrams**.
- Business Idea Pitching, Elevator Pitch.
- Black-box and White-box Testing.